Welcome back to my series where I
recreate Ben & Jerry's flavors, but
lower in calories and higher in protein.
This is marshmallow sky. Let me show you
how to make it. In your Ninja Creamy
Pint, you're going to combine 400 g of a
fat-free high protein milk, some vanilla
bean paste, some sweetener, salt,
zantham gum, and then a little bit of
blue food coloring. Then we're going to
use about half a serving of mini
marshmallows. You can just throw these
in at the end. The creamy will mix them
in for you. And you just throw that in
the freezer for about 16 hours. Take it
out, run it under hot water for about a
minute, and then throw it in your creamy
on the light ice cream setting. You
might need to respin a couple of times.
Mine came out good the first time, but
once it looks about like this, we can
grab our toppings. We're using some of
the best protein cookie dough in the
game right now from Fuel Snacks. I'm
using about half a package and then 5 g
of these little mini marshmallows. And
then all that's left to do is throw
those on top, mix them in by hand, and
you are good to go.